我对僵尸有一点困惑
Here's what I wonder about zombies.
要是他们找不到人肉吃会怎么样
What happens if they can't get any human flesh to eat?
他们不可能饿死  他们本来就是死人嘛
They can't starve to death-- they're already dead.
你听听我的  我昨晚花了一个小时在想
You take this one. I spent an hour last night on
"既然吸血鬼在镜子里
"How do vampires shave
都看不见自己  他们是怎么给自己剃胡子的"
when they can't see themselves in the mirror"?
衣冠楚楚的吸血鬼两两搭伴
Well-groomed vampires meet in pairs
互相刮胡子  解释完毕
and shave each other-- case closed.
好吧  那  僵尸呢
Yeah, okay, so, zombies.
我觉得这取决于僵尸的种类  拉杰
I guess it depends on the zombies, Raj.
我们现在说的是快僵尸还是慢僵尸
Are we talking slow zombies, fast zombies?
在《28天》里面  如果那些僵尸不吃东西
Like, in 28 Days, if those zombies didn't eat,
-他们就会饿死  -你说的是
- they starved.  - You're thinking
《惊变28天》
of 28 Days Later.
《28天》里面桑德拉·布洛克去戒酒
28 Days is where Sandra Bullock goes to rehab
结果让观众升华到濒死状态
and puts the audience into an undead state.
喂  不许你说桑德拉·布洛克坏话
Hey, don't bag on Sandra Bullock!
你以为这样显得很有内涵
You think it makes you look cultured,
但你表现出来的只是刻薄而已
but you just come off as bitter.
12点方向  希伯特博士
Oh, Dr. Siebert, twelve o'clock.
为啥大学校长
Why's the president of the university
要来食堂里视察呢
slumming in the cafeteria?
也许他在模仿莎翁笔下的亨利五世
Perhaps he's emulating Shakespeare's Henry V,
微服私访  想知道在民间
who dressed as a commoner and mingled among them,
他的臣民们是如何看待自己的
to find out how he was being perceived by his subjects.
当然  如果他看过我发给他的1300封
Of course, if he'd have read any of the 1,300 e-mails
关于学校管理的邮件中的任何一封
I've sent him on the subject of his administration,
他就不必这么费劲了
he could have saved himself the trouble.
也可能是因为他听说今天周二有炸薯棒
Or maybe he heard it's Tator Tot Tuesday.
反正我是因为这个才来的
That's why I'm here.
嗨  我最器重的天才们
Hey, there's my favorite geniuses!
今天过得怎么样啊
How are we doing today?
这取决于  你打算
That depends-- how much longer
在我的肩膀上抚摸多久
do you plan on fondling my shoulder?
抱歉  库珀博士  我忘了你有爱抚恐惧症
Sorry, Dr. Cooper, I forgot you have a touch phobia.
我不是怕人抚摸  我是怕细菌
It's not a touch phobia, it's a germ phobia.
要是你愿意戴一双乳胶手套
If you'd like to go put on a pair of latex gloves,
给我查疝气都没问题
I'll let you check me for a hernia.
好吧
Yeah.
听好了各位
So, listen, fellas,
本周六晚上谁想去参加一个小宴会呢
who's up for a little party this Saturday night?
美酒  佳肴  没准儿还会有几位甜妞
Open bar, good eats, might even be a few pretty girls.
听起来很赞啊  我去
Sounds great! I'm in!
慢着
Hold on.
就因为一位怪蜀黍给你们糖吃
Just because the nice man is offering you candy,
并不意味着你就应该跳进人贩子的破车里
doesn't mean you should jump into his windowless van.
究竟是什么场合啊
What's the occasion?
就是本校的几位赞助者
Just a little fund-raiser for the university.
啊哈  沾满泪痕的气垫还在车后面呢
Aha! The tear-stained air mattress in the back of the van.
你不情愿我很理解  库珀博士
I understand your reticence, Dr. Cooper,
我深表同情  但残酷的事实摆在面前
and I sympathize, but the hard facts are,
有时候我们不得不为了募集研究资金
occasionally, we have to shake a few hands
而跟某些人溜须拍马
and kiss a few butts to raise money for our research.
我不管  这太下作了
I don't care; it's demeaning.
我不愿想像只德州博览会的冠军猪一样
And I refuse to be trotted out and shown off
被人领着到处表演
like a prize hog at the Texas State Fair.
顺便提一下  这种博览会肯定不是你想穿着
Which, by the way, is something you don't want to attend
别有星际迷航徽章的衣服参加的
wearing a Star Trek ensign's uniform.
好吧
All right,
那我换个说法
let me put it this way.
你们都得给我穿好正装参加这个宴会
You're gonna put on a suit, you're gonna come to this party,
你们要向一群老人解释
and you're gonna explain your research
你们所做的研究
to a bunch of old people,
否则  我对天发誓  我会用热勺子烫瞎你的眼睛
or I swear to God, I'll blind you with a hot spoon,
就像《贫民窟的百万富翁》里的那个小男孩一样
like they did to that little boy in Slumdog Millionaire.
你肯定不想那样的
Oh, you don't want that.
那就周六晚上咯
So, Saturday night!
包你开心
It's gonna be off the hook.
速度拿开
Get over it.
哦天啊
Oh, boy!
又是炸薯棒又是宴会邀请
Tator tots and a party invitation?
今天是个好日子啊
What a great day!
生活大爆炸
第四季第十五集
好了
There you go.
你确定这样就行了
Are you sure this is right?
嗯  把这一段塞到裤子里  就没事了
Yeah, just tuck that part in your pants; you'll be fine.
一起去给拍那些有钱人的马屁吧
Okay, let's go smooch some rich, wrinkled tochis.
霍华德  我真不敢相信伯纳黛特居然让你
Oh, Howard, I can't believe Bernadette let you go
穿着女式衬领去参加这么正式的宴会
to a fancy party wearing a dickey.
不好意思  我的衣服不是我女朋友挑的
Excuse me, my girlfriend doesn't pick out my clothes.
是我妈挑的
My mother does.
我们该出发了
Oh. We should get going.
那谢尔顿呢
What about Sheldon?
谢尔顿不去
Sheldon is not going.
真的假的  那我们怎么跟希伯特交待
Really? What do we tell Siebert?
告诉他库珀博士觉得他宝贵时间最有价值的用途
Tell him Dr. Cooper feels that the best use of his time
就是运用他那举世罕见的天赋
is to employ his rare and precious mental faculties
来揭开自然的面纱  目睹上帝的真面
to tear the mask off nature and stare at the face of God.
谢尔顿  现在是周六晚上  你要去洗衣服了
Sheldon, it's Saturday night, you'll be doing laundry.
别跟他说这个  说揭开面纱啥的
Don't tell him that, tell him the mask thing.
喂  把领带塞回裤子里
Hey, put your tie back in your pants.
这地儿不错啊
Nice place.
让我想起了我爸妈在新德里的房子
Reminds me of my parents' house back in New Delhi.
-别逗了  -真的  我家很有钱的
- You're kidding.  - No. We are very wealthy.
但跟这里唯一的区别就是  我们的仆人更多
But the only difference is, we have more servants.
-比这儿还多啊  -多得没地儿使唤
- More than this?  - More than we can use.
你看吧  在印度  我们都不会犯
You see, in India, we don't make the mistake
让人们有梦想这种错误
of letting our poor people have dreams.
我的牛人小队来了
Ah. There's my band of brainiacs.
库珀博士在哪儿呢
Where's Dr. Cooper?
他正在揭开自然的面纱  目睹上帝的真面
He's tearing the mask off nature to look at the face of God.
校领导认定他有颗美丽心灵
The board of directors insists he has a beautiful mind.
我认为他就是浮云
I think he's just bananas.
来吧  我来介绍你们认识一位
Come on, let me introduce you
咱们学校的主要捐款人
to one of the university's leading donors.
我觉得咱们被他们所谓的美女误导了
I think we were misled about the cute girls.
莱森女士  这是我们学校
Mrs. Latham, I'd like you to meet three
三位了不起的青年学者
of our outstanding young researchers.
这位是莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德博士
This is Dr. Leonard Hofstadter,
拉杰·库萨帕里博士和霍华德·沃罗威茨
Dr. Rajesh Koothrappali and Howard Wolowitz.
沃罗威茨你怎么了
Well, what happened to you, Wolowitz,
坚持不下去读博么
couldn't stick with it long enough to get your PhD?
我是工程师
I'm an engineer.
工程师通常不需要博士学位
Most engineers don't bother with a PhD.
不过你没准想知道
But you may be interested to know
我给NASA设计过零重力废物排放系统的
I designed the zero-gravity waste-disposal system for NASA.
懂了  你就是太空水管工
Got it-- you're a space plumber.
我去吧台喝两杯
I'm gonna go hit the bar.
介绍这两位吧
Tell me about these two.
先介绍他
Do him first.
霍夫斯塔德博士今天晚上会做个我们实验物理项目的演讲
Dr. Hofstadter is representing our experimental physics program tonight.
我想你会对他迷人的工作感兴趣的
I think you'll really enjoy hearing about his fascinating work.
行吧
Right.
迷我一下
Fascinate me.
他们快要尿裤子的样子很可爱吧
They're cute when they're about to wet themselves, aren't they?
这么说吧
I'll make it easy for you.
每天早上你到实验室的第一件事
When you arrive at the lab in the morning,
你会最先打开什么机器
what sort of machine do you turn on?
咖啡机
Coffee maker?
行吧 库那什么博士  到你了
All right, Dr. Kooth-- uh, whatever it is-- you're up.
我叫库萨帕里
It's Koothrappali.
我得去嘘嘘了
I have to tinkle.
于是  我没有屈服于权贵
And so, instead of bowing to pressure,
去参加那个毫无意义的社交晚会
and going to that pointless soiree,
而是待在家里  把衣服都洗了
I stayed right here and did a load of whites.
通常我会赞许你那反社会的大男子气概
Well, normally I respect your macho rebellious attitude
不听你们领导的
toward "The Man,"
但这回  我觉得你犯了个愚蠢的错误
but, in this case, I think you've made a foolish mistake.
不可能
Unlikely.
但请你说完
But make your case.
请记住  您那批评的语气
Keeping in mind that your critical attitude
正毁坏咱们周六夜晚的美好时光
is ruining our Saturday night together,
我都没有把你窗口最小化
and I'm not above minimizing your window.
谢尔顿  不管你喜不喜欢
Sheldon, like it or not,
在你能把你的智慧
until you manage to upload your intelligence
上载到一颗自给自足  装备着高速互联网
into a self-sustaining orbiting satellite,
和隐形设备的轨道卫星上之前
equipped with high-speed Internet and a cloaking device,
你还是需要依靠其他人类同胞的
you will be dependent on other members of the human race.
够了  我要把你最小化了
That's it. Prepare to be minimized.
我还没说完
I'm not finished.
谢尔顿  所有科学家都要去募集资金
All scientists have to fund-raise, Sheldon.
你觉得我的实验室靠的是什么资金
How do you think I paid for my lab?
我去了沙特阿拉伯  遇到个王子
I went to Saudi Arabia and met with a prince
他正好对神经生物学感兴趣
who had an interest in neurobiology.
你的实验室靠中东业余爱好者资助的么
Your lab is funded by some Middle-Eastern dilettante?
更准确地说  法伊萨是我未婚夫
Technically, Faisal is my fianc?
但我现在有最高端的双光子显微镜
But I do have a state-of-the-art two-photon microscope
冬天去利雅得(阿拉伯半岛中部的城市)还有个住所
and a place to stay in Riyadh for the winter.
终于明白你Facebook上面那些诡异的骆驼比赛的照片
Well, that explains those puzzling camel race photos
是哪里来的了
on your Facebook page.
你这么想
And consider this:
如果物理学院没有你出面
without you to make the case for the physics department,
募捐的重任就落到莱纳德和拉杰那种人头上了
the task will fall to people like Leonard and Rajesh.
你唬我么
Are you trying to scare me?
你成功了
'Cause you're succeeding.
等着更恐怖的吧
Well, then prepare to be terrified.
如果你的朋友们没有足够说服力的话
If your friends are unconvincing,
今年的捐款可能就被
this year's donations might go to,
地质学院卷走了
say, the geology department.
不要吧  那些烂泥研究员
Oh, dear, not the dirt people!
或者更糟糕
Or worse-- it could go to...
也可能给人文学院哦
the liberal arts.
不要
No!
几百万的捐款都在那些骚人墨客
Millions of dollars being showered on poets,
身上打了水漂
literary theorists and students of gender studies.
噢  人文啊
Oh, the humanities!
往好处想  我觉得希伯特校长再也不会
On the bright side, I don't think President Siebert
让我们参加任何募捐活动了
will be making us go to any more fund-raisers.
受戒仪式都没这么痛苦
It was so much easier at my bar mitzvah.
那些老家伙也就捏捏你的小脸蛋
The old people just came up to you, pinched your cheek
就把储蓄债券给了你
and handed you a savings bond.
别这么闷闷不乐嘛
Oh, don't be such gloomy Gusses.
看这的虾有多大
Look at the size of these shrimp!
到多大就可以叫做龙虾了
At what point do we start calling them lobsters?
承认吧  我们搞砸了
Face it, Raj, we crashed and burned tonight.
没那么糟糕啦
Oh, you didn't do that badly.
莱瑟姆女士  我每天早晨第一个打开的机器
Mrs. Latham, the first machine I turn on in the morning
是氦氖激光器  给它预热
is the helium-neon laser, 'cause it needs to warm up.
亲爱的我不关心
I no longer care, dear.
别着急
But don't worry,
今天晚上见到你们很高兴
I really enjoyed meeting you this evening.
别开玩笑了  哪里值得高兴了
You're kidding. That was good for you?
我出了一身汗了
'Cause I was sweating through my T-shirt.
最好不过了
Excellent! There's nothing I like better
我最喜欢调戏聪明人了
than making smart people feel ill at ease.
啥
Why?
你有了钱之后
Oh, I don't know, it's one of the fun things
就喜欢找这种乐子
you get to do when you have lots of money.
看着
Watch.
谁让你吃这里的虾了
Hey! Who said you could eat that shrimp?
有趣吧
See? Fun.
不不不  我只是来要钱的
No, no, no, I'm just here for your money.
我不想握任何人的带菌手
I don't want to shake anyone's germy hands.
希伯特  快跟他们说清楚
Explain it to them, Siebert.
我必须承认
I must confess
我不懂你什么意思  希伯特校长
I don't understand you, President Siebert.
你一开始说你想要我出席你的筹款会
First you say you want me to appear at your fund-raisers,
现在你又说你再也不想让我
but now you say you never want me to go
接近你的筹款会
anywhere near your fund-raisers.
不好意思  但您这意思有点混乱呀
Forgive me, but that sounds like a mixed message.
又来了
Here we go again.
如果你懒得跟我讲话的话
If there's simply no talking to me,
那干吗还打电话给我
why did you call?
对不起  另一条线上有电话进来了
I'm sorry, someone's on the other line.
你何不组织一下你的语言
Why don't you see if you can organize your thoughts,
我们晚点再聊
and we'll try again later.
库珀和霍夫斯塔德家  简称库珀家
Cooper-Hofstadter residence. Go for Cooper.
早上好  莱森太太
Good morning, Mrs. Latham.
当然  我当然记得你
Well, yes, of course I remember you.
一个通过把死去丈夫得来的
A woman well past her prime
不义之财都捐赠出去以提高自己的
seeking to augment her social status
社会地位的女人
by doling out her late husband's ill-gotten gains.
那你准备给我多少钱
So, how much money are you going to give me?
我不疯  我妈带我检查过的
I'm not crazy -- my mother had me tested.
如果你不准备给我钱
Well, if you're not going to give me money,
那你打电话来干嘛
then why are you calling?
她要跟你讲话
She wants to talk to you.
到底谁才是疯子
Who's crazy now?
你好  莱森太太
Hello, Mrs. Latham.
是的  我跟他住在一起
Yes, I live with him.
我不  我也不知道为什么
I don't...I-I really don't know why.
今晚吗  好的  没问题
Tonight? Sure, that'd be great.
好的  到时见
Okay, I'll see you then.
再见
Bye.
她想跟我共进晚餐  谈谈我的研究
She wants to have dinner and talk about my research.
就你那点研究还用得着整个晚餐的时间来讨论吗
An entire dinner to talk about your research?
你们去哪吃  免下车的魔术盒快餐[美国快餐店]吗
Where you going, the drive-thru at Jack in the Box?
不管去哪都好
Well, wherever we're going,
她会派车来接我
she's sending a car to pick me up.
好吧
Okay,
-我明白了  -明白什么了
- I see what's happening.  - What?
我的境界吓到她了
My stature intimidates her,
所以她就利用你来接近我
so she's using you to get to me.
狡猾的老师太
Crafty old gal.
不好意思  但你并不是这间公寓里唯一
Excuse me, but you are not the only
一名出色的科学家
distinguished scientist in this apartment.
我在同行评审刊物里发表过论文
I've been published in peer-reviewed journals,
我在实验粒子物理学方面获得过
I received a Dissertation of the Year award
年度专题论文奖
for experimental particle physics.
不  不可能
No, that can't be it.
还有你似乎忘了
And since you seem
咱俩住在一起
to have forgotten, the reason we live together
是因为咱俩是死党
is we're best friends.
我会挺你的  杰克
And I got your back, Jack.
-晚餐棒极了  -很高兴你喜欢
- That was a great meal.  - I'm glad you enjoyed it.
我唯一一次吃得这么好  就是我妈来看我
The only time I eat this well is when my mom's in town
-然后带我出去吃饭那次  -是吗
- and she takes me out to dinner.  - Is that so?
你跟她有点像
You kind of remind me of her.
她也喜欢把人弄得不自在
She enjoys making people uncomfortable, too.
你让我想起我在大学时期的男朋友
Well, you remind me of a boy I dated in college.
-不会吧  -很可爱的男孩
- No kidding.  - Sweet boy.
非常聪明
Very smart.
要是他有钱就好了
If only he'd had money.
说到钱
So, hey, speaking of money,
你想不想帮物理系添置一个
how are you feeling about helping the physics department
低温离心泵和一个分子筛
get a cryogenic centrifugal pump and molecular sieve?
我只能说  你很有说服力
Well, I must say, you make a very persuasive case for it.
-太好了  太好了  -而我真的
- Oh, good, good.  - And I'm seriously
在考虑要进一步发展
considering taking it to the next level.
太棒了  这太好了
Terrific. Great.
怎么个进一步发展法
What level is that?
现在你不像我妈了
Okay, now you don't remind me of my mom.
对不起  也就是说  最终僵尸会
I'm sorry, so, eventually, zombies are going to attack
袭击桑德拉·布洛克[美国女演员]所在的戒酒中心吗
the rehab facility where Sandra Bullock is?
没错  谢尔顿  继续看吧
Yes, Sheldon. Keep watching.
这太可惜了
You know, it's a shame,
她那么费劲地要戒酒
all that work she's doing to get sober,
结果就为了被生吞活剥
only to be torn apart and eaten alive.
晚餐怎么样
Hey. How was dinner?
一级棒  我得喝上一杯
Swell. I need a drink.
我们还有酒吗
Do we have any alcohol?
没有  但是我们有土豆  我可以给你做伏特加
No. But we have potatoes -- I could make you vodka.
不过要两周才能做好
It'll take two weeks.
莱纳德  你没事吧
Leonard, are you okay?
我不确定
Um, I'm not sure.
怎么了
What's going on?
莱森说她在考虑要给我们捐钱
Well, Mrs. Latham said she was seriously considering
好让我们买一个
donating money so we could get
低温离心泵
a cryogenic centrifugal pump...
太棒了
Yes!
然后她就把舌头伸进我嘴里了
...then she stuck her tongue down my throat.
为什么
Why?
我们不能总是每件事都解释给你听
Okay, we can't keep explaining everything.
自己去看看我们买给你的那本书
Read that book we got you.
她喜欢我
She hit on me.
等一下  等一下  等一下  你是说
Wait-wait-wait. Are you telling us
那个老师太想要跟你上床
that old lady wanted to have sex with you
作为给你的院系捐赠上百万美金的条件吗
in exchange for giving your department millions of dollars?
好像是
I think so.
你个幸运的小鸭子
You lucky duck.
你还真是够扭曲的啊
You're really a broken toy, aren't you?
我赶在她有下一步行动之前
I was able to get out of there
就逃回来了
before anything else happened,
可她明晚还想见我
but she wants to see me again tomorrow night.
太棒了  你准备穿什么
Excellent! What are you planning to wear?
什么
What?
佩妮  你在用肉体
Penny, you're an expert
来交换物质这反面是专家
on trading sexual favors for material gain --
教教他
walk him through this.
不不  等一下
Well, n-no, hold on a second,
我才不要跟她上床呢
I'm not going to sleep with her.
但是我们需要低温离心泵
But we need a cryogenic centrifugal pump.
想也别想  我才不会这么做呢
Well, forget it! It's not gonna happen.
拜托  莱纳德  这可能是你
Well, come now, Leonard, this may be your only chance
为科学做贡献的唯一机会了
to make a real contribution to science!
我重申一遍  不可能
I repeat, not gonna happen.
你刚才说我出卖肉体来交换物质
What was all that about me trading sexual favors
是什么意思
for material gain?
这是赞美
It was a compliment.
我觉得值得赞美的时候就该赞美
I believe in giving credit where credit is due.
好的  我会转告他
Okay, fine. I'll tell him.
莱纳德  莱森太太的车在楼下等你
Leonard, Mrs. Latham's car is here for you.
我一会儿就回来  我就下去为经费
I won't be too late; I'm just gonna make
做最后一次努力  再跟她道声晚安
a final pitch for the funding and then say good night.
等等  我有东西要给你
Hold on, I have something for you.
这是什么
What's this?
你今晚可能会用到的东西
Just a few things you may need tonight.
BB油  保险套  还有
Baby oil, condoms and, uh...
我在医药学院搞来的小药丸
a little something I procured from the school of pharmacology.
他们说这是伟哥中的战斗哥
They say it is to Viagra as Viagra is to a green M&M.
我不会跟她上床的
I am not going to have sex with her.
或许这个能帮助你克服你的不情愿
Maybe this will overcome your reluctance.
为了激发你的性欲  我上网找了
I went on the Internet and found a photograph
一张莱森太太25岁时的照片
of a 25-year-old Mrs. Latham to get your libido humming.
看她穿着马鞍鞋呢  嗷~
Check out those saddle shoes.
你脑子进水啦
Are you insane?
我才不会为了几台新设备
I'm not going to prostitute myself
就出卖自己的肉体呢
just so we can get some new equipment.
拜托  何乐而不为呢
Oh, come on! Why not?
晚安  谢尔顿
Good night, sheldon.
鉴于你用于毫无意义的自慰所花费的大量时间
Given how much time you spend engaging in pointless self-abuse,
不妨考虑一下  就这一次
you might consider, just this once,
让自己的生殖器达到真正合体的高潮
using your genitalia to actually accomplish something!
他还是不愿意献身给那个老女人  对吧
He still won't shag the old lady, huh?
对  多谢关心
No. But thank you for asking.
你好
Hey. Hi.
你好  莱纳德
Hello, Leonard.
希望你饿了
I hope you're hungry.
我饿得不行不行的
I'm very hungry.
仅限于对食物  是吧
For food, right?
昨晚我让你不安了吧
Oh, I made you uncomfortable last night.
真是抱歉
I'm so sorry.
没关系
No, that's okay.
不  你肯定在说违心话
No, it most certainly is not.
莱纳德  不管咱们之间发生了什么
Leonard, I'm making the donation to your department
我都会给你的实验室捐款
regardless of what happens between us.
-真的吗  -当然
- Really? - Well, of course.
现在又不是等价交换
There's no quid pro quo here.
你和你的同事们从事的研究十分杰出
You and your colleagues are doing remarkable research,
这笔钱是你们应得的
and you deserve the money.
好吧
Oh.
那昨晚算怎么回事
Then what was last night about?
我试了一把  告我啊
I took a shot; sue me.
好吧
Oh.
莱纳德  你长得真帅
You're a very handsome man, Leonard.
谢谢
Thank you.
我真傻  以为像你这样血气方刚的年轻人
It was foolish of me to think someone your age
会对我这样熟透的大龄熟女感兴趣
might ever be interested in someone like me.
别这么说
Oh, don't say that.
-你是一个很魅力的女人  -拜托
- You're a very attractive woman. - Oh, please.
-我是说真的  -你小嘴真甜
- No, it's true. - Well, aren't you sweet.
我得重申一遍
Just for the record...
与妾共度一夜  君将余生齿颊留香
you'd remember a night with me for the rest of your life.
那是当然
I'm sure I would.
不过为什么这么说
But why-why, exactly?
你是个聪明人
You're a very smart man.
你认为我得有多大的本事  才能傍上一个这么有钱的丈夫
How do you think I landed such a rich husband?
我还真没想过这个问题
I hadn't really given it much thought.
那好好想想吧
Well, think about it.
难不成你是指
Do you mean...?
正确  老娘就是有本事让男人爽
Yep. I'm that good.
牡丹花下死  做鬼也风流
Oh, what the hell.
早安  荡夫
Good morning, slut.
说啥呢
What?
拜托  我一眼就看出来了  你的步伐充满羞愧
Oh, please, I recognize the walk of shame when I see it.
你缺少的只是花掉的睫毛膏
All you're missing is a little smeared mascara
和卷成一团塞在坤包里的小裤裤
and a purse with panties wadded up in it.
-发生什么事了  -没事
- What's going on? - Oh, nothing's going on.
借光
Excuse me.
-你才回来  -是
- Are you just getting home? - Yeah.
这是个好兆头  对吧
That's a good sign, right?
的确
Oh, yeah.
我为你而自豪
I'm so proud of you!
你就像普通站街女一样
You sold yourself out
出卖了自己的肉体
like a common streetwalker!
不  我不是为了钱而做
No, I didn't do it for the money.
她爽完就跑了
She stiffed you?
我认为应该是你的室友这么对人家吧
I believe that's what your roommate did to her.
搞毛啊
What?!
再说一遍  多读读我们给你那本书
Again, read the book we gave you.
不是这样的  我是说
No, I mean,
她一开始就把钱给我了
I-I got the money first.
聪明  先收钱后办事
Smart. Get paid up front.
我发现你有当小白脸的潜质呀  莱纳德
Yeah, I think you have a real knack for gigolo work, Leonard.
我要进去歇着
I'm gonna go lie down.
这个主意不错  养精蓄锐
That's a good idea; get your rest.
外面有大把有钱又饥渴的老女人
There are a lot more rich old ladies out there,
而哥正好需要一台新的直线加速器
and Daddy needs a new linear accelerator.
亏我当时还觉得
And I thought he didn't
他没有从你们的恋爱中学到任何东西
learn anything from his relationship with you.
说啥呢
Hey!
这是赞美
Another compliment!
你得学着去识别
Learn to recognize them.
他来了
Ah, there he is!
当前最令人瞩目的人
The man of the hour!
他牺牲小我  完成大我
He took one for the team!
我真不是为了钱
I didn't do it for the money!
这样自我安慰也不错  至少能让你好过点
Keep telling yourself that-- it makes it easier.
相信我  我深有体会
Trust me, I know.
-厉害啊  伙计  你真了不起  -就是
- Cool, buddy! That's awesome! - Yeah!
老师太  给力不
How was she?